{
    "subject": "resource/Goodfellas",
    "predicate": "property/language",
    "object": "English",
    "human_readable": "The language of the film Goodfellas is English.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9778474569320679,
            "question": "Is the film Goodfellas spoken in English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9108707904815674,
            "question": "In what language is the movie Goodfellas spoken?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8881056308746338,
            "question": "Is Goodfellas a film with English dialogue?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8836439847946167,
            "question": "Is English the dominant language in Goodfellas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8618474006652832,
            "question": "What language was the film Goodfellas made in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7970142364501953,
            "question": "What is the primary language used in the film Goodfellas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7297865152359009,
            "question": "Which language do the characters speak in Goodfellas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6813550591468811,
            "question": "What language would be necessary to understand the plot of Goodfellas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6647219061851501,
            "question": "Can you identify the language used by actors in Goodfellas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33996179699897766,
            "question": "Would someone need subtitles to understand Goodfellas?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The language of the film Goodfellas is English.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7901_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you identify the language used by actors in Goodfellas?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7901_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What language would be necessary to understand the plot of Goodfellas?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7901_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which language do the characters speak in Goodfellas?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7901_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7901_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7901_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7901_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7901_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7901_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7901_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7901_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7901_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7901_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7901_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that \"Goodfellas\" was released in the United States with an English-language version, which supports the statement that the language of the film Goodfellas is English."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}